Hello have you ever tried to or perhaps are contemplating how to plan an amicable divorce?
That for sure is the ideal divorce.
My name is Dr. Felicia and I'd like to share a few tips with you about planning that divorce.
The first thing that would happen is of course for it to be amicable is both persons would have to agree that they want the divorce.
Now that may happen overtime, it could happen early on in the marriage or later in the marriage depending on the couple.
But the thing is to bridge the topic of divorce gradually, slowly, let them know that you're not happy about certain things, let the other party know that you'd like to talk about it, if you can't talk about it and reach a resolution, then you'd like to make an amicable divorce so that, or separation so that you both have certain things that you need.
The best way to make it amicable is to be fair, not to be greedy to allow for equal acquisition, disposition of your assets and to help each other perhaps through the transition period.
That's the ideal method of making an amicable divorce.
If you can do that and communicate like that, you're ahead of many couples.
I do wish you good luck, Dr. Felicia signing off.